import React, { createContext, useState } from 'react';
const MyContext = createContext();
export const ContextProvider = ({ children }) => {
  const [data, setData] = useState([
    { description: 'What is Paris? ğŸ—¼', question: 'Capital of France ', answer: 'Paris ğŸ—¼', status: false },
    { description: 'What is 4? â—', question: 'Square root of 16 ğŸ§®', answer: '4ï¸âƒ£', status: false },
    { description: 'What is blue? ğŸŒŒ', question: 'Color of the sky ğŸŒ¥ï¸', answer: 'Blue ğŸ”µ', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Pacific? ğŸŒŠ', question: 'Largest ocean ğŸŒ', answer: 'Pacific ğŸŒŠ', status: false },
    { description: 'Who is Biden? ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¸', question: 'President of the USA ğŸ›ï¸', answer: 'Biden ğŸ‘”', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Oxygen? ğŸ§ª', question: 'Element with symbol O ğŸ§¬', answer: 'Oxygen ğŸ§ª', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Venus? ğŸ”¥', question: 'Hottest planet ğŸŒ•', answer: 'Venus ğŸ”¥', status: false },
    { description: 'Who is Rowling? ğŸ“š', question: 'Author of Harry Potter ğŸ§™â€â™‚ï¸', answer: 'Rowling ğŸ–‹ï¸', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Everest? ğŸ”ï¸', question: 'Tallest mountain â›°ï¸', answer: 'Everest ğŸ”ï¸', status: false },
    { description: 'What is the Sun? â˜€ï¸', question: 'Closest star to Earth ğŸŒ', answer: 'Sun ğŸŒ', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Yen? ğŸ’´', question: 'Currency of Japan ğŸ—¾', answer: 'Yen ğŸ’´', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Red? ğŸŸ¥', question: 'Primary color red ğŸ¨', answer: 'Red ğŸŸ¥', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Seven? ğŸŒ', question: 'Number of continents ğŸ—ºï¸', answer: 'Seven 7ï¸âƒ£', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Hydrogen? ğŸ§ª', question: 'First element in the periodic table ğŸ”¬', answer: 'Hydrogen ğŸ§ª', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Square? â—¼ï¸', question: 'Shape with 4 equal sides ğŸ”²', answer: 'Square â—»ï¸', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Portuguese?', question: 'The main language in Brazil ğŸ—£ï¸', answer: 'Portuguese ', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Water? ğŸ’§', question: 'Common name for H2O ğŸ§Š', answer: 'Water ğŸ’§', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Saturn? ğŸ’«', question: 'Planet known for rings ğŸª', answer: 'Saturn ğŸ’«', status: false },
    { description: 'Who is Washington? ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¸', question: 'First President of the USA ğŸ›ï¸', answer: 'Washington ğŸ‘”', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Sahara? ğŸœï¸', question: 'Largest desert ğŸŒ', answer: 'Sahara ğŸœï¸', status: false },
    { description: 'Who is Holmes? ğŸ•µï¸â€â™‚ï¸', question: 'Main character in Sherlock Holmes ğŸ•µï¸', answer: 'Holmes ğŸ”', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Nile? ğŸï¸', question: 'Longest river ğŸŒ', answer: 'Nile ğŸŒŠ', status: false },
    { description: 'What is China?', question: 'Most populous country ğŸŒ', answer: 'China ğŸ¯', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Pound? ğŸ’·', question: 'Unit of currency in the UK', answer: 'Pound ğŸ’·', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Thermometer? ğŸŒ¡ï¸', question: 'Device for measuring temperature ğŸ§ª', answer: 'Thermometer ğŸŒ¡ï¸', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Photosynthesis? ğŸŒ±', question: 'Process of converting sunlight into food â˜€ï¸', answer: 'Photosynthesis ğŸŒ', status: false },
    { description: 'Who is Fitzgerald? ğŸ“–', question: 'Author of The Great Gatsby ğŸ–‹ï¸', answer: 'Fitzgerald ğŸ“š', status: false },
    { description: 'What is Gravity? ğŸŒ', question: 'Force that attracts objects toward the Earth ğŸ§²', answer: 'Gravity ğŸŒ', status: false },
    { description: 'Who is Einstein? ğŸ§ ', question: 'Theoretical physicist who developed the theory of relativity ğŸ”¬', answer: 'Einstein ğŸ§ ', status: false },
    { description: 'What is DNA? ğŸ§¬', question: 'Molecule that carries genetic information in living beings ğŸ§‘â€ğŸ”¬', answer: 'DNA ğŸ§¬', status: false },
  ]);
  return (
    <MyContext.Provider value={{data}}>
      {children}
    </MyContext.Provider>
  );
};

export default MyContext;
